http://www.beck-liner.com/external_privacy_policy

Navigation
HomeAbout usHistoric timelineVision and valuesSustainabilityBeck - a great place to work!Code of conductAwardsProductsWhy frozen foods block liners?The Beck LinerThe Beck Freezing FrameBeck-LaseEjectorsTrolleysPlate FreezersPassionate about qualityISO 9001/ISO 22000/FSSC 22000SENASA CertificateService and supportManual: Frozen foods blockFAQPersonal contactAgentsJobsCareer PortalContactManagementSales and servicesMedia
External Privacy Policy for Beck Pack Systems A/S
Beck Pack Systems A / S (in the future "we", "our", "us") takes your data protection seriously as a data controller. We process personal data and have therefore adopted this Privacy Policy which tells you how we process your data. At the same time, we ensure that your personal data is processed in accordance with the law.
Processing of personal data:
Personal data is any kind of information that can be attributed to you to some extent.
In order to be a customer, supplier, and/or business partner with us, we need to collect the following personal data about you:
Name.
E-mail.
Address
Payment details.
Phone number etc.
This information is collected based on the following legal bases: Consent, contract fulfillment, balancing of interests.
If you do not want us to process this information, it may be problematic to maintain and accommodate any agreements made.
Security:
We have taken appropriate technical and organizational measures to prevent your information being accidentally or illegally erased, published, lost, impaired or misunderstood, misused or otherwise treated in violation of law.
Purpose:
Personal information about customers is collected for the following purposes:
Processing your purchase and delivery of our service
Managing your relationship with us
Personal information about suppliers and business partners is collected for the following purposes:
Processing our purchase/services
Managing your relationship with us
Data Minimization:
We collect, process, and store only the personal data necessary to fulfill our purpose as stated.
Data is kept up to date:
Since our service is dependent on your data being accurate and up-to-date, we ask you to keep us informed about changes in your data. If we become aware of data that is not correct, we will update the information.
Disclosure of information:
We use a number of third parties for the storage and processing of data, including suppliers of IT solutions and suppliers for the distribution of goods. They only process information on our behalf and may not use it for their own purposes. In relevant cases, data is passed on to banks and debt collection.
We only use data processors in the EU or secure third countries, as well as companies in countries that can provide your information with adequate protection.
Your rights:
You have the right to gain insight into the information we process about you, as well as the right to correct in inaccurate information about you.
Upon request, we can inform you of the data we process about you. However, access may be restricted due to the privacy of other persons, business secrets, and intellectual property rights.
You can use your rights by contacting us.
Contact info:
Appeals:
You have the opportunity to complain about our processing of your personal data to the Data Inspectorate, the mail address is dt@datatilsynet.dk.
Contact
+45 5695 2522
info@beck-liner.com
